

# DAVID CANO ZAFRA

PHYSICS AND BIOMEDICAL ENGINEER

ADRESS C/RESIDENCIA, BARCELONA C/ MARIA DE GUZMAN, MADRID

**NUMBER** 629985034

E-MAIL DAVID.CANO221@GMAIL.COM

**WEBPAGE:** https://davidcano221.github.io/davidcano/

## PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

Physics engineer with a Master of Science in Biomedical Engineering. Currently coursing a Master of Science in Data Science and Engineering. 1-year experience investigating digital biomedical signals. I consider myself a curious person willing and able to learn fast and constantly improve. I can adapt to different scenarios providing perspectives from the mathematical, physics, and engineering fields.

#### **EDUCATION**

MSC DATA SCIENCE AND ENGINEERING **CURRENTLY** 

WEBPAGES CREATION, PROGRAMMING, **AND DESIGN 2020** 

E-LEARNING TRAINING 2020

MSC BIOMEDICAL ENGINEERING 2018 - 2020

BSC PYSHICS ENGINEERING 2014 - 2018

#### LANGUAGES

**SPANISH CATALAN ENGLISH GERMAN** 

# **EXPERIENCE**

RESEARCHER - UPC SEPT. 2018 - JAN. 2020

- · Acquisition, filtering and visualization of digital biomedical signals.
- · Utilization of Matlab and Python.

# STUDENT SUPPORT - UPC

MAR. 2018

• To inform college students who are interested in the degree about the features of it.

CUSTOMER SUPPORT - DECATHLON JUNE 2017 - SEPT. 2017

- To attend and support the customer.
- To help the teammates of other departments.

### PROGRAMMING SKILLS



**PYTHON** 



R



MATLAB



**TABLEAU** 



**EXCEL** 

SOL

SOL

# PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

VERSATILITY RESPONSIBILITY

WILLINGNESS PROBLEM TO LEARN SOLVING

**TEAMWORK** ASSERTIVENESS